Rensselaer W. Lee Papers, 1930-1984 (bulk 1960-1980 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Tasso: Photographs: Tempesta, undated; 1 folder (Folder 13)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research Notes: A. Parma Tiarini "Including Notes of 1979", undated; 1 folder (Folder 14)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research Notes: Tiepolo, 1875-1979; 1 folder (Folder 15)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research Notes: Benjamin West, 1946-1970; 1 folder (Folder 16)
- Tasso: Photographs: Vouet, undated; 1 folder (Folder 17)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research Notes: Vouet's "Rinaldo and Armida", 1913-1969; 1 folder (Folder 18)
- Tasso: Research Notes, undated; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Tasso: Research Notes: "Important Pages of Writing previously used or cut from something already written", undated; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Tasso: "Erminia in Minneapolis" Drafts, 1980; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Tasso: Research Notes: MOLA Article "For Blunt's Volume", 1966; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Tasso: Van Dyck Article (Baltimore Museum of Art), 1946-1959; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Van Dyck Article: Preparatory Material- Photographs, undated; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Tasso: Van Dyck Photographs, 1909-1954; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Tasso: Duplicate Photographs (for an article?), undated; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Tasso: Research Notes/Photographs: "Notes and Letters for E.P. Paper", 1959; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Tasso: Photographs Request 1930's, 1920-1954; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Binder of Notes, undated; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Tasso: Miscellanea "Important", 1954-1979; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Tasso: Lecture and Publication: "Observations on the First Illustrations of Tasso's Gerusalemme Liberata", 1957-1982; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Tasso: "Observation..." Drafts and Notes, undated; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Tasso: Research Notes, 1764-1975; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Tasso: Research P.U. Holdings, undated; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Tasso: Research Correspondence, 1936-1978; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Tasso: Research: Solerti, 1983; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Tasso: Research/Photographs: Italy, 1969; Tramontano (Sorrento), 1969-1970; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Tasso: Research: "Notes on Tasso and the Turks, undated; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Tasso: Research: Venice and London, 1896-1978; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Tasso: Research/Photographs: Claude Lorrain (Attrib.): Herriana and Marcel Roethlisberger, 1980; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Tasso: Research: Xerox A. Bellori, "Gli Epigoni..." (Padoua), 1893; 1 folder (Folder 12)
- Tasso: Xerox Summary of Conquistata and Liberata, undated; 1 folder (Folder 13)
- Tasso: David Quint Article, 1984; 1 folder (Folder 14)
- Tasso: Research Misc., 1971-1984; 1 folder (Folder 15)
- Tasso: Photographs: Anonymous Book Illustrations late 18th Century and 19th Century, 1720-1980; 1 folder (Folder 16)
- Tasso: "Odd Notes"; Misc. Research and Correspondence and Photographs, 1830-1978; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Tasso: Research Europe 1957, 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Tasso: Research: "Important Notes: Tasso and Tivoli Catalogue", 1939-1957; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Tasso: Research/Photographs: Seriss from Chateau de Chenailles (now Toledo); Comparative Material, 1956-1971; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Tasso: Research, 1936-1958; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Tasso: Research, 1957-1958; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Tasso: Research "Notes: Tasso", 1938-1958; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Tasso: Misc. Research and Correspondence, 1958-1965; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Tasso: Research Notes and Correspondence, 1954-1974; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Tasso: Research Mahon Notes, 1821-1964; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Tasso: Research and Drafts: Photographs, 1955-1961; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Tasso: Research (also Lomazzo): "Important Notes", 1955-1958; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Tasso: Research: Solimena, 1956 May; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Tasso: Research: Tiepolo, undated; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Tasso: Research (also Ariosto?), 1921-1963; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Tasso: Other Media, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Tasso: "Tasso Paper for Gertrude Coor", 1959; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Tasso: Research "Bibliographical Odds and Ends- Tasso and Tramontana Edition Notes for G.L.", 1940-1950; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Tasso: Xeroxes Aminta- British Museum, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Tasso: Photographs Madrid-Armida Story, undated; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research Notes: Tapestries- Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1973-1988; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Tapestries, 1939-1974; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Research/Photographs: Paris, 1963-1978; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research: Frescoes-Veneto, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research: Vienna Series, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research: 18th Century French Snuffbox (Correspondence with Anthony Blunt), 1974; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research: G.C. Bevilacqua Drawings (Padua and Venice), 1972-1977; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Tasso: Photographs: Paolo Finoglia (d. 1656), undated; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Tasso: Photographs: Fontebasso Drawings (Albertina), 1977; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Tasso: Photographs: Luca Giordano, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 12)
- Tasso: Photographs: Gaetano Lapis (1706-1758) Urbino, undated; 1 folder (Folder 13)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research: Paolo di Matteis, 1936-1978; 1 folder (Folder 14)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research: MOLA Drawings; Pommers Felden, Etc., 1966-1976; 1 folder (Folder 15)
- Tasso: Research: Letters on MOLA Drawings, 1966-1969; 1 folder (Folder 16)
- Research in Europe, 1956-1977; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research: "For London 1978", 1928-1968; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research, 1950-1973; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Photographs: "Comparative Material" "Rome, Church of San Vitale", undated; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Tasso: Photographs: "Supplementary Material", 1899-1976; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Tasso: Photographs: "Problems of Identification", undated; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Tasso: Paintings to be Checked: Photographs, 1934-1961; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Photographs: Negatives, undated; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Tasso: Photographs (Frick), 1819-1930; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Tasso: Photographs: Rinaldo/Armida (Alnwick Castle), 1952; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Tasso: Research: Aminta List; MOLA; Berlin List; Delacroix, undated; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Tasso: Research: "Notes from London and Paris" Ricci, A. Carracci, Delacroix, undated; 1 folder (Folder 12)
- Tasso: Photographs: Villa Barbieri, San Lazzaro, Bologna, undated; 1 folder (Folder 13)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research: Buccleugh Pictures, 1946-1955; 1 folder (Folder 14)
- Tasso: Photographs: "Germany, England, Holland, Denmark", 1912-1931; 1 folder (Folder 15)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research Guercino, 1911-1969; 1 folder (Folder 16)
- Guercino Giovannino, Cento, undated; 1 folder (Folder 17)
- Photographs/Research: Palazzo Moroni, Bergamo, undated; 1 folder (Folder 18)
- Bibliography of Illustrated Editions of Tasso: Original, undated; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Bibliography of Illustrated Editions of Tasso: Xerox, undated; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Tasso: Photographs/Research: 1609 Edition of Conquistata and Liberata, undated; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Tasso: Research: French Editions, 1952-1955; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Tasso: Photographs: Tasso Editions: Ciatti 159_; Vincenti 1611; Prati 1613; Sarzina 1625; Corbi (sp.?) c. 1735; Misserina 1624; Tozzi 1628, 1590-1735; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Tasso: Photographs: Tasso Editions: Paris 1667; Paris 1671 and 1678; Paris 1771; Paris 1784, 1667-1784; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Tasso: Photographs: Tasso Editions: Curti 1665, 1611-1665; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Tasso: Research: Tasso Editions: Rome 1670 and 1674, 1670-1674; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Tasso: Photographs: Tasso Editions: Piazzetti 1745; Gioffo 1760; T_? 1784; Lafi 1778; Prati 1817-1822, 1745-1822; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Tasso: Research: Tasso Editions: Italy 19th Century- 1820, 1823, 1840, 1841, 1895, 1820-1895; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Tasso: Photographs: Tasso Editions: England 18th Century, 19th Century, 1611-1939; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Tasso: Photographs: Tasso Editions: Paris 1803; 1810 (2); 1815, 1803-1815; 1 folder (Folder 12)
- Tasso: Photographs: Tasso Editions: Paris 1836, 1841, 1823, 1822, 1852, Tours 1876, 1822-1876; 1 folder (Folder 13)
- Tasso: Photographs: Tasso Editions: German- Frankfurt 1626 or 1651; Rottendam 1658, 1626-1658; 1 folder (Folder 14)
- Tasso: Photographs: Tasso Editions: 1817 and 1844, 1817-1844; 1 folder (Folder 15)
- Research: Tasso Conquistata at Haruard and other authors, 1635-1982; 1 folder (Folder 16)
- Ariosto: Research: "Notes on Tasso: Discarded Work on Editions. But Watch for Ariosto", 1955; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Ariosto: Editions: Information on Editions: Bergamo, Vatican, Ferrara, Etc., 1933-1938; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Ariosto: Editions: "Miscellaneous from the Ottava d'Oro", undated; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Ariosto: Editions: G.G. di Ferreri 1542; Zoppino 1530; Valvassori 1556 and 1566; Valgrisi 1566, 1530-1566; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Ariosto: Editions: Valvassori 1553 Etc., 1534-1554; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Ariosto: Editions: Sessa (1609); Varisco (1563); Varisco (1568); Rampazetto 1549 (sp.?), 1549-1609; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Ariosto: Editions: Perchachino 1567; Ramp(f?)azetto 1549; Rampazetto 1565, 1549-1567; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Ariosto: Editions: Farri 1580; Polo 1583 (1563 Venice); Franceschi 1584; Angelieri (?) 1585; Misserino 1600 (1582); Orlandini 1730, 1583-1730; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Ariosto: Editions: Paris, 1720 (from Bibl. Nat.) and others, 1566-1844; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Ariosto: Editions: Zatta 1772 Folio Ed. Ferrara, 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Ariosto: Editions: Zatta 1772 (Vatican), 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Ariosto: Editions: Baskerville 1773; Paris (Cochin) 1775; Paris 1839 (Raab); Paris 1844 (Madeleine), Etc., 1773-1900; 1 folder (Folder 12)
- Ariosto: Editions: Paris, 1839 (KNAB), 1 folder (Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous: Ariosto, undated; 1 folder (Folder 14)
- Ariosto: Research/Photographs: Misc., 1930-1984; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Ariosto: Research, undated; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Ariosto: Research: Notes by Leslie Brown, 1904-1969; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Ariosto: Research: Dosso's Melissa and Fragonard's Angelica, undated; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Ariosto: Research: Perseus/Pegasus, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Ariosto: Research/Photographs: "Annibale Caracci" Etc. (includes other paintings), 1925-1978; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Ariosto: Research/Photographs: Chiusa di Pesio Frescoes, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Ariosto: Research/Photographs: Angelica Kauffman, 1925-1973; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Ariosto: Research: Mahon, 1952; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Ariosto: Research: Malvasia and Couwenbergh, undated; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Ariosto: Research/Photographs: Villa Mondragone, 1973; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Ariosto: Correspondence and Photos: Velasquez "Angelica and Medore", 1935-1942; 1 folder (Folder 12)
- Ariosto: Photographs, 1937-1973; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Ariosto: Photographs Miscellaneous, 1975; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- "Orlando Furioso": Rerro's of Drawings, undated; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Ariosto: Photographs: Maiolica, undated; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Ariosto: Photographs: Canto X, 1902-1978; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Ariosto: Photographs: Canto XI, undated; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Ariosto: Photographs: Canto XIX, 1969; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Ariosto: Photographs: German, Flemish, Spanish, Etc., undated; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Ariosto: Photographs: France and Rubens, 1934-1954; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Ariosto: Photographs: Fragonard, 1932; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Photographs: Fragonard Drawing's "Orlando Furioso", undated; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Ariosto: Photographs: Italian Artists, 1864-1982; 1 folder (Folder 12)
- Ariosto: Photographs: Bologna, undated; 1 folder (Folder 13)
- Ariosto-Tasso: Photographs: Engravings of Valesio (Albertina), undated; 1 folder (Folder 14)
- Ariosto: Photographs: Villa of Monsoni, Agordo Paoletti Prescoes, undated; 1 folder (Folder 15)
- Ariosto: Photographs: Dosso Dossi, Etc., 1931; 1 folder (Folder 16)
- Publications: Misc., 1940; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Ariosto: "Names on Trees" Publication, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Ariosto: Publication of "Names on Trees: Ariosto into Art" P.U.P., 1976-1978; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Ariosto-"Names on Trees": Permissions to Reproduce Photographs for Publication, 1917-1976; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Ariosto: "Names on Trees": Lectures, undated; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Ariosto: "Adventures of Angelica: Early Frescoes Illustrating the Orlando Furioso" Drafts, undated; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Ariosto: "Adventures of Angelica" Proofs Made in Florence including author's Note Never Attached, 1976; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Article (Ariosto): "Addenda to Angelica", 1980-1981; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Ariosto: "Ariosto and Art" Draft, undated; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- "Ariosto Parts from Meiss Lecture", 1991; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Ariosto: "Ariosto's Roger and Angelica in Sixteenth Century Art: Some Facts and Hypothesis" Galley for Meiss Festschrift, undated; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Ariosto: Meiss Festschrift Drafts, 1977; 1 folder (Folder 12)
- Ariosto Lectures, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Folder 13)
- "Botticelli Lecture", 1941; 1 folder (Folder 14)
- Genoa: Photographs, 1912-1970; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Genoa: Writers/Literature; Misc. Research, 1974; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Genoa: Gianvincenzo Imperiale Research- Heckscher and Misc., 1984; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Genoa: Marcellus Petrarch, 1958; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Genoa: Xerox of Ezia Gavazza, La Grande Decorazione a Genova (Genova, 1974), v. 1, 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Genoa: Palazza Doria, 1956-1970; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Genoa: Palazza Posta Vecchia Research/Photographs, 1981; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Genoa: Photographs: Palazzo Posta Vecchia and Palazzo Centurione, 1955; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Genoa: Research/Photographs: Palazzo Scassi including Livy, undated; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Genoa: Further Research on Livy; Research/Photographs: Sala Dei Capitani, Palazzo Senatori, Frescoes by T. Laureti, 1977-1984; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Genoa: Castello Biography, 1978; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Genoa: Castello Xeroxes of V. Belloni and F. Poleggi, 1969; 1 folder (Folder 12)
- Genoa: Castello Paggi Letters, undated; 1 folder (Folder 13)
- Genoa: Castello Tasso Editions 1617, 1604-1617; 1 folder (Folder 14)
- Genoa: Castello in Genoese Palaces, also "Embriaco" Research, 1978; 1 folder (Folder 15)
- Genoa: Castello Drawings and Frescoes: Photographs/Research, undated; 1 folder (Folder 16)
- Genoa: Castello Drawings: Photographs/Research, 1976; 1 folder (Folder 17)
- Genoa: Castello: Offprint on Castello Drawings, 1979; 1 folder (Folder 18)
- Genoa: Chiabrera; Ceba Research, undated; 1 folder (Folder 19)
- Research: Misc. Offprints/Articles, 1975-1984; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Research: Aretino/Art Theory, 1964-1976; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Research: Aretino and Titian ("Painters and Poets"), 1980-1982; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Marino Research, 1961-1966; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Research: Marino La Galleria... 1620 Xerox, 1620-1979; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Research: Marino and Artists, 1982-1984; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Research:Chiabrera, 1838; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Research:Poets and Painters (Petrarch; Grillo), 1859-1979; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Research:Poets and Painters (Botticelli), 1945-1978; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Correspondence: Recommendations, 1940-1984; 6 folders (Folder 1-6)
- Mirka Benes, 1974-1984; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Charles Carmen, 1976-1984; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Tracy Cooper, 1957-1984; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Elizabeth Cropper, 1975-1984; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Charles Dempsey, 1972-1984; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Rona Goffen, 1975-1982; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Carla Gottlieb, 1949-1984; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Archer St. Clair Harvey, 1975-1984; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Edith Kirsch, 1968-1982; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Linda Klinger, 1980-1984; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Ut Pictura Poesis, 1943-1982; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Ut Pictura Poesis: Notes "The Ancients", undated; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Ut Pictura Poesis: Art Bulletin 1940 "Camera Copy", 1940-1967; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Article (Tasso): D. Mona, undated; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Article: "Erminia in Minneapolis", 1964-1967; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Tasso: "Poetry into Painting: Tasso and Art" Lecture Drafts (Given at Middlebury College), 1969-1970; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Article: "Giambattista Tiepolo's Drawing of Rinaldo and Armida" (Tasso), 1961; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Article: "Observations on the First Illustrations of Tasso's Gerusalemme Liberata" (Tasso), 1980-1982; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Tasso: Torquato Lecture, 1956; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Lecture: "New Wine in Old Bottles" (Notes), undated; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Publications Misc.: Book Reviews and Articles, 1928-1954; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- Autobiography/CV, 1968-1985; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- Eulogies; Addresses; Testimonials (Inluding Princeton University) See also under Indiv. Organizations, 1953-1980; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Humor- Misc., 1965-1980; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Richard Krautheimer, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Millard Meiss, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- Charles Rufus Morey, 1955 December; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Erwin Panofsky, 1934-1978; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Wolfgang Stechow, 1952-1975; 1 folder (Folder 8)
- Richard Stillwell, 1977-1982; 1 folder (Folder 9)
- Kurt Weitzmann, 1967-1984; 1 folder (Folder 10)
- Various Bound Volumes, 1928-1981; 1 folder (Folder 11)
- G.W. Bowersock N.Y. Review of Books Offprint, 1980 March 6; 1 folder (Folder 1)
- S. Haynes Burlington Magazine Offprint, 1979 November; 1 folder (Folder 2)
- Isa Ragusa Review of 19th Century American Artists and Italy Offprint, 1983; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- W.S. Heckscher Offprint from Art the Ape of Nature, 1981 June 2; 1 folder (Folder 4)
- Bryn Mawr Alumnae Bulletin, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Folder 5)
- "Creativity" and "Tradition" by Paul Oskar Kristeller Offprint, 1983; 1 folder (Folder 6)
- Various Bound Volumes, 1948-1984; 4 folders (Folder 7-10)
- Various Bound Volumes, 1946-1986; 2 folders (Folder 1-2)
- Kidder Smith- Muslim Architecture, 1961-1963; 1 folder (Folder 3)
- Various Bound Volumes, 1938-1977; 2 folders (Folder 4-5)
- Various Bound Volumes, 1945-1981; 4 folders (Folder 1-4)
- Various Bound Volumes, 1940-1981; 6 folders (Folder 1-6)
- 32101040813220 (Box 1)
- 32101040813238 (Box 2)
- 32101040813246 (Box 3)
- 32101040813253 (Box 4)
- 32101040813261 (Box 5)
- 32101040813279 (Box 6)
- 32101040813287 (Box 7)
- 32101040813295 (Box 8)
- 32101040813303 (Box 9)
- 32101040813311 (Box 10)
- 32101040813329 (Box 11)
- 32101040813337 (Box 12)
- 32101040813345 (Box 13)
- 32101040813352 (Box 14)
- 32101040813360 (Box 15)
- 32101040813378 (Box 16)
- 32101040813386 (Box 17)
- 32101040813394 (Box 18)
- 32101040813402 (Box 19)
- 32101040813410 (Box 20)
- 32101040813428 (Box 21)
- 32101040813436 (Box 22)
- 32101040813444 (Box 23)
- 32101040813451 (Box 24)
- 32101040813469 (Box 25)
- 32101040813477 (Box 26)
- 32101040813485 (Box 27)
- 32101040813493 (Box 28)
- 32101040813501 (Box 29)
- 32101040813519 (Box 30)
- 32101040813527 (Box 31)
- 32101040813535 (Box 32)
- 32101040813543 (Box 33)
- 32101040813550 (Box 34)
- 32101040813568 (Box 35)
- 32101040813576 (Box 36)
- 32101040813584 (Box 37)
- 32101040813592 (Box 38)
- 32101040813600 (Box 39)
- 32101040813618 (Box 40)
- 32101040813626 (Box 41)
- 32101040813634 (Box 42)
- 32101040813642 (Box 43)
- 32101040813659 (Box 44)
- 32101040813667 (Box 45)